Introducing Anon and Son. Both
of them are professional advocates.
Anon has lots of pressure and workload
every time due to his work pressure. He
puzzled during important dates where
he fails to solve cases.
And sometimes he gets
trouble. Because of his
anger and pressure of
his day to day works.
On the other hand, so on, on ordinary
advocate and a colleague of Anon.
Not a genius, but he
managed well and make report of each
requirement to related work in just few
clicks and few moments.
Within that because he installed
on his workspace Garuda.
We
are presenting Karada on
ultimate workspace for advocates
which unrequired we'll
ever work concrete. Get your
Garuda now. Don't become an owl. Be an
eagle. Thank you.